pizzapizza.ca 2013-05-08

# Our Privacy Policy | Pizza Pizza

**Our Privacy Policy**  
Pizza Pizza is committed to protecting the Personal Information you provide. Our Privacy Policy explains how we handle your Personal Information. Personal Information includes your name, address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, postal code, town/city, gender, purchase history, click through activity, food preferences and any and all other information you may provide on our website, through our telephone Contact Centres, letters or email through the “Customer Feedback” feature of our website.

 **Your Consent**  
Each time you visit this website, place an order through our Call Centres or provide us with information you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information by Pizza Pizza in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

 **Changes to Privacy Policy** ****  
Please review this privacy policy periodically as it may be updated from time to time. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be effective and binding to you immediately following the posting of such changes to this website. This Privacy Policy was last reviewed on April 4, 2008. Please also see our website´s “Terms of Use” for other terms and conditions governing your use of our website, products and services.

 **Cookies** ****  
Like most websites, the Pizza Pizza Website uses cookies to keep track of your purchases and other activity on the website and enhance your experience on the website. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password and, if you choose, to save other Personal Information so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the site. Third party advertisers on the website may also place cookies on your browser. If you wish to disable these cookies, the “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how. However, if you set your browser to disable cookies, you may not be able to access certain areas on the website.

 **Storage of Personal Information**  
We store the Personal Information you provide to us in our computer databases. We own, maintain and operate our computer servers containing our databases. We use firewalls and other security measures to protect our servers.

 **Collection, Use and Disclosure of Personal Information** ****  
We use the Personal Information about you stored in our database in various ways. First, the next time you use our online web ordering and enter your User ID and Password, we will call-up your information from our database to make processing your order faster and easier.

We also keep track of your food preferences and restaurant choices and analyze that information.

Pizza Pizza may use Personal Information for fulfilling your order or other fully disclosed purposes, such as to enter you into a contest, speed-up the placing process for a future orders or responding by email to an inquiry that you posted online. Your Personal Information may also be used by Pizza Pizza, or any other division of Pizza Pizza, to contact you regarding other products or services that may be of interest to you (including those that we may offer jointly with other companies) and for our customer appreciation programs.

We will not give, sell, rent or loan any of your Personal Information to any third party (with the exception of third parties performing functions on our behalf who have an obligation to keep your information completely confidential or a third party who buys our business) unless you have authorized us to do so.

Pizza Pizza reserves the right to access and/or disclose Personal Information where required to comply with applicable laws or lawful government requests or, in Pizza Pizza’s reasonable opinion, to operate the Pizza Pizza Website or Contact Centres properly and securely, or to protect Pizza Pizza or visitors to this website.

To process transactions on the site or via our Contact Centres, we may share your Personal Information with our agents, representatives, contractors and service providers so they can provide us with support services such as authorization of credit card transactions, placing of orders and order fulfilment and promotional fulfilment. We require these entities not to use your information for any other purpose.

Your Personal Information may be passed on to a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership or assets or a bankruptcy of Pizza Pizza. We may also disclose your Personal Information to our subsidiary and parent companies and businesses, and other affiliated legal entities and businesses with whom we are under common corporate control. However, all of these parent, subsidiary and affiliated legal entities and businesses that receive your Personal Information from us will comply with the terms of this privacy policy with respect to their use and disclosure of such Personal Information.

 **Removal of Personal Information**  
You may at any time contact the Pizza Pizza Contact Centre through your local ordering telephone number or at 416-967-1111 in order to have your Personal Information removed from our database.

 **Unsubscribe or Opt Out** ****  
If you wish to stop receiving communications from Pizza Pizza, log in to your Pizza Pizza “My Profile,” select “Modify Your Profile,” uncheck the box that states “Yes! I would like to be the first to know about new promotions, contests and money saving offers from Pizza Pizza,” and click “Update My Profile.”

 **Links to Other Sites** ****  
The Pizza Pizza Website may offer links to other sites not operated by Pizza Pizza. If you visit one of these sites, you should review their privacy and other policies. Pizza Pizza is not responsible for the policies and practices of others. ****

 **How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, the practices of this website or our Contact Centre, or your dealings with the website or our Contact Centre, you can contact us at privacy@pizzapizza.ca. You can also send us mail to:

Privacy Officer  
Pizza Pizza Limited  
c/o Legal Department  
500 Kipling Avenue  
Toronto, ON  
M8Z5E5

Toll Free: 1-800-265-9762  
In Toronto: 416-967-1010
